<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Krista L. DeStasio</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Krista L. DeStasio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a scientific researcher and aspiring programmer interested in creating usable interfaces through data driven insights. While I have learned a great deal of programing through self-instruction, I decided in Fall of 2019 to attend Lane Community College for formal training in computer programming and am currently studying to earn an Associate of Applied Science in Computer Programming.
I earned an M.S. in Psychology from the University of Oregon where I was a National Science Foundation Graduate Research Fellow in the Social and Affective Neuroscience Lab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>Krista L. DeStasio, M.S. E-mail: kdestasio@gmail.com
GitHub: https://github.com/kdestasio
Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kdestasio/
SKILLS Proficiency: R, R Shiny, Git/GitHub, MacOS, Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Statistics
Familiarity: Python, MATLAB, HTML/CSS, JSON, Linux CentOS &amp;amp; RHEL, Excel
Exposure: C#, SQL, Oracle, Singularity, Docker, SLURM
RELEVANT EXPERIENCE GRADUATE LEVEL RESEARCHER
Social and Affective Neuroscience Lab, University of Oregon
2016 – 2019
 Developed computer tasks in PsychoPy to present visual stimuli and collect participant responses https://github.com/kdestasio/child_task and adapted extant MATLAB tasks for use in new studies based on user feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clustering Analysis of Dot Probe Data</title>
      <link>/post/summary_threatbias/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/summary_threatbias/</guid>
      <description>This post walks through an exploratory k-means clustering analysis as applied to numerical data from a dot probe task. Steps to preprocess and analyze the data are discussed and the results are presented through visualizations, as well as a discussion of the results. All code used in the analysis and in the production of this blog post is available at https://github.com/kdestasio/hc_analysis. For additional resources on clustering, see the references section at the bottom of the post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Best Practices</title>
      <link>/post/r_best_practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/r_best_practices/</guid>
      <description>When learning to write code for research projects, it can be overwhelming to figure out how to set-up a project and the novice programmer may not yet have the experience necessary to forsee potential pitfalls of a given, seemingly inconsequential decision. This post provides a discussion of best practices1 for developing code-based projects and for writing R code in a research setting with an eye toward proactively avoiding common pitfalls.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>